But I did have this same tumor when I was a kid...
可我还是孩子时得过同种肿瘤...
same exact tumor.
一模一样的肿瘤
Mine was on my femur, and it was bigger.
我的在我股骨上 更大
We caught it later than we caught J.J.'s.
发现得也比他的晚
We treated it, and look at me.
我们接受治疗了 看看我
I'm here, Michelle. I'm alive.
我在这里 米歇尔 我还活着
So, you had it?
所以 你得过这病
And you survived it?
然后你活下来了
Unless I'm a ghost.
除非我是鬼
He's gonna be so scared.
他会很害怕
Yeah, there's gonna be scary moments, for sure.
是 确实会有很可怕的时候
For me, the scariest part was seeing how sad my mom was all the time.
对于我来说 最可怕的是看到我妈妈一直这么伤心
And losing my hair, but that's 'cause...
和失去我的头发 可那 因为...
Look at this hair.
看这茂密的发量
That's it. That's what J.J. needs to see,
这就对了 这是他需要看到的
a little bit at least, every day.
每天至少有一点点
- Okay. - Okay?
-好  -好
So, let it out and come back in when you're ready.
那就这个状态 你准备好以后就进来